Overall: 
•	dont use large dashes (“—") 
•	Use larger Skill-in logo in all slides
•	The headline of each slide (top-right grey font) cab barely be seen – make it highlighted (perhaps use glowing yellow or think about something)
Slide1: 
•	in the bottom use “skill-in.com” instead of skill-in.io” + make this highlighted (currently you can barely see it)
Slide2: 
•	the headlines “companies” and Jon Sekkers” need to be highlighted, larger and each with a different colour for distinction “ Company – blue, Job seeker – green (same like in other slides)
•	Remove the “Interviews” from the Company side (the platform will not replace interviews). Instead, use “Home Exams” – and think about a bad thing to say about it (e.g. can be faked with ai etc).
•	The last item of the companies should start with “Bad hire:” and coloured white. 
•	Last item on the job seeker side should be about the fit that with traditional hiring the candidate has no way to know if the organization fits his style (choose good wording, and same structure like having the first 2 words in white e.g. “Organization fit:”
Slide3: 
•	Highlight (in white font) “reverse-engineered” and “real project”
•	Code Quality should also include behavioural signals like number commits, velocity, prs success rate (I don’t know – you think of something better. I don’t want  an additional check item , just making this item more up to date with todays programming which is mainly vibe coding). By the way, you can add additional check item but then you should also add to the company skillset side, to be symmetric.
Slide4: 
•	Remove “5 min”
•	Can barely see connect icon because f the colors.
•	General correction: it is not about scoring. It is about finding patterns and generate textual description of them, like an AI skill. So remove “Review AI scores” from the Calibrate box. The employer doesn’t have to review it. And change the main diagram of the slide to a suitable one (including the employer rating and weights input) 
Slide5: 
•	The “Employer” headline is almost touching the “profiles in the marketplace” headline. So make the entire table lower in the page (you have plenty of room)
•	Remove “reviews scores”
•	Make the ‘Platform Receives” box with orange (glowing) color on both sides (because green belongs only to employer side)
•	Remove “Project brief”. Instead use “Difficulty level” (or choose your own wording, but remember the course is shaped by tech requirements + design content. The design content is out of scope for the employer).
•	Replace the content of “Shallow filter first” (including the headline) . It should be about candidate selects a project according to desired role, skills, tech stack…(its parallel to a step where candidates apply for a specific job)
•	Remove “across all 4 data buckets” since we are removed from the apples to apples approach.
•	In “Platform receives” of the candidate side, replace the “Their photo” to “Their fit rate”, or something like that – you choose. The idea is that a candidate succeeds in a course shaped by a specific employer is a perfect fit, but still, candidate profile goes in the platform’s DB so the platform now activates the Matching engine sending pushes to both employers and the candidate when finding a match.
•	The Marketplace diagram, now between the Employer and the Candidate, should be located below, and horizonal for a better layout. 
•	The “MARKETPLACE”, “Sr. Backend Eng.” And “Backend Dev” labels can barely be seen. Change their color to white. 
Slide6: 
•	Remove “and privacy validation”, instead say “and MCP servers”
•	Remove “- nothing sensitive leaves”  (that’s obvious)
•	Change “ Privacy filter: strips content, keeps metrics” to “Calls tools APIs|
•	Make the arrows color glowing yellow (currently can barely be seen)
•	The following labels should be white (can barely be seen now): Context & permissions, Orchestration prompt, Credentials (remove “never leave”), Reads context · calls tools · asks for human ratings · (Remove “applies scoring”) · decides what to submit, ↓ normalized metadata only
↓ anonymized scores only (change the scores to something else like assessment – I already mentioned it before), Counts, ratios, frequencies · no message content · no code, Scores 0–100(change this!)  per dimension · no names · no PII
•	Change “Stays on machine” to “Kept Safe” (actually, think about the best wording for this that will relax the employer)
•	Change “Aggregated scores (0–100)” to the proper description of assessment content to be used by ai.
Slide7:  The slide is not needed – remove it
Will tell you later about the other 4 slides. For now make the changes
